(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-05T14:45:39.497821",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
こんばんは！
Good evening!
わんわん！
Wan wan!
わわわーい！ わわわーい！
Wawawa-i! Wawawa-i!
チワワじゃないよ！ ふわわだよ！
I'm not a chihuahua! I'm Fuwawa!
ふわわじゃないよ！ もここだよ！
I'm not Fuwawa! I'm Mococo!
もここじゃないよ！ パトラだよぉ！
I'm not Mococo! I'm Patra!
三人合わせて…
Together as three...
せーの！ わわわ、わんわん、わわわ、わわわ…
Ready, set! Wawawa, wanwan, wawawa, wawawa...
籠り出すヒューズをアン・ドゥ
Unlocking the locked-up fuses,
こんばんはー！
Good evening!
お疲れ様でしたー！
Thank you for your hard work!
やっつけちゃいそう！ やる気満々だよ！
We're gonna beat it! We're super motivated!
みんなさんに3Dでコラボをお届けしちゃうよー！
Delivering a 3D collab to everyone!
やっとパトラとちょっとコラボできるの嬉しいだー！
I'm so happy we finally get to collab with Patra!
前回はマシュマロで色々お話しましたけど、今日はこんな姿で色々ねー
Last time we talked about all sorts of things with marshmallows,
but today in this form...
おもしろい時間を過ごしたいです！
We want to spend a fun time!
え、パトラお姉ちゃんって、お姉ちゃんですか？
Eh, Patra big sis, are you an older sister?
はーい、こんばんはー！ 蘇生パトラです！
Hii, good evening! It's Suou Patra!
なんとなんと、私がフワモコのASMRボイスを作りましたー！
Believe it or not, I made FuwamoCo's ASMR voices!
すごーい！ めちゃくちゃすごい！ いやでも、なんか今日もすごいところに呼ばれたなってー
So amazing! Absolutely amazing! But you know,
we feel like we were called to an amazing place today...
え、皆さんどうですか？
Eh, how is everyone?
なんか配信来た時よりもパワーアップしてんだよね！
It's even more powered up than when we streamed before!
あ、なんか、どう？ どうなの？
Oh, like, how is it? How's it going?
ドーナツもそう！ かわいい！ ドーナツもお耳じゃなくて、ドーナツ！ かわいい！
The donuts too! So cute! The donuts aren't ears,
they're donuts! Cute!
うんうんうん！
Mhm mhm!
なんか、カニプリン！ カニプリン！ 美味しいものがたくさん飛んでる！ あの、お耳以外をね！
Like, crab pudding! Lots of delicious things are flying,
except for the ears!
お耳以外いい！ 黄色のね、パワーアップしたお耳もあるし！ やっとんだっていうね！
Other than ears is good! There are even yellow,
powered-up ears! Finally found out, huh!
お耳ピオリーですね！ お耳ピオリが！
Ear-pioli, huh! Ear-pioli is here!
ありまーすね！ 前はね、ちょっとお話とか色々ありましたけどー
There is! Before, we had all sorts of chats and stuff, but...
今回のコラボが、なんでこのスタジオと見ますと、パトラお姉ちゃんプロデュースのフワモコASMRボイスが発売されたからねー！
As for why this collab is in this studio, it's because
Patra-neesan produced FuwamoCo ASMR voice was released!
発売されたからねー！ フワモコASMRボイスが！
It's been released! The FuwamoCo ASMR voice!
はい、今回はね！
Yes, this time!
うん！
Yeah!
フワモコボイスと英語ボイスが
With lots of Fuwawa and Mococo voices
いっぱい！アニメーションやったー！
and English voices, an animation! Yay!
色んなじゃあ楽しめる
Speaking of wonderful ASMR
素敵なASMRといえばはい パトラお姉ちゃんですね。
that you can enjoy, yes, it's Patra-neesan.
さん、ありがとう！
Um, thank you!
え、だから今日パトラがご褒美もらえるって聞いてきたんですけど
Um, so I heard Patra gets a reward today, but...
そのこんなね、あのちょっと、ね、あの不思議な耳は置いといて
Leaving aside this, you know, a bit strange ear...
え、なんかね3Dでせっかく習うんだからね
Um, since we're finally learning in 3D,
ちょっと、なんかこうくっついたりとかさ、したいなって思って
I thought it'd be nice if we could get close together!
うんうんうん、ほらほらほら
Yeah yeah yeah, look, look, look!
あ、あ、あ、しよ、しよ、しよ、よしよしよし！
Ah, good, good, good!
ぽんぽん、ぽんぽんぽん！
Pat, pat, pat, pat, pat!
いや、いいわもう、もこちゃんともこちゃんど
Yeah, that's good, Mococo and...
ぽんぽんぽん、ぽんぽんぽん！
Pat, pat, pat, pat, pat!
はあ、もう満足しましたね！
Ah, I'm already satisfied!
満足したよ！
I'm satisfied!
そうでも、今度のフワモコASMRボイスはパトラお姉さんのスタジオで
But this time's FUWAMOCO ASMR voice is at Patra-neesan's studio...
そうなんですよ。フワモコも初めてのASMRだからさ、すごく緊張してドキドキがやばくて
It's Fuwawa & Mococo's first ASMR, so we were super nervous and our hearts were beating!
本当にね、あの収録しているときに
Truly, while recording,
え、パトラお姉ちゃんこれで大丈夫？
"Um, Patra-neesan, is this okay?"
え、かわいい、びっくり終わって。もうね、全てが可愛いからね
"Eh, so cute!" We finished and everything was just so cute!
オッケーです！オッケーです！
"Okay! Okay!"
めちゃくちゃね、あの抵抗、あ、NG抵抗パトラも持ってるからね。
There's a lot of resistance, ah, Patra has NG resistance too.
いつもはじまりのね、もこちゃんもね、お腹すごいグルグルなってたよね。
And always at the start, Mococo's stomach was rumbling so much!
お腹でしょ？そう、ドキドキだけじゃなくて
In her stomach? Yeah, not just from the nerves...
そうです！緊張もね、緊張しました！
That's right! We were nervous too!
え、だから、そう、かわいいな！
Eh, so, yeah, so cute!
え、あの、ちょっと色々始まる前にやっぱりね、大事なことをやらないといけないと思うんですよ。
Um, before everything starts, I think we need to do something important.
大事な。そうそうそうそう。やっぱね、パトラお姉ちゃん、両耳だから！
Important. Yeah, because Patra-neesan has both ears!
え！いや、あのね、リアルにね、こうね、パトラをバイノーラルマイクだと思って
Eh! Realistically thinking of Patra as a binaural mic...
ささやくの、大事だと思いません？
Whispering is important, don't you think?
オッケー。じゃあ、もこちゃん、ちょっとこれね、プレゼントで。プレゼント！
Okay. So, Mococo, here's a present. A present!
うん、オッケーです！
Yeah, okay!
はい。あ、いつでもパトラお姉ちゃん！
Yes. Ah, anytime, Patra-neesan!
ぱおぱお、ぱおぱお！ありがとう！すごい英語、ありがとう！
Pao pao! Thank you! Amazing English, thank you!
じゃあ、パトラ、今日はもう帰って、あ、はじまったパトラです。
Well, Patra, go home today... ah, Patra who has started.
そうだよ！ぜひぜひね、配信見てるみなさんもね、フワモコのエスエムアールボイスを聞いてください！
That's right! Everyone, please listen to FUWAMOCO's ASMR voice!
おもきょうはね、特別なハッシュタグとかもあります！
Today, there's also a special hashtag!
はすてい！プリーズ！ハステイ！ハステイ！さあ、フワモコバッスリーディー！
Hastay! Please! Hastay! Now, FUWAMOCO 3D!
ね、たくさんのスィクショとか感想をつぶやいてくださいね！
Please tweet lots of your thoughts and impressions!
でもやっぱさ、3Dになるとさ、我々はやっぱり目立ちますよね、いろいろ。いろいろ目立つ目立つ！
But when it's 3D, we really stand out, don't we? Standing out!
フワモコも目立つよ！ま、可愛い！小さいってことは武器だ！
FUWAMOCO stands out too! Cute! Being small is a weapon!
ぱおぱお、ぱおぱお！
Pao pao, pao pao!
じゃあ、やっぱね、横こうね、横向くかね、よく分かるかも、カメラさん。
Well, if we turn sideways, you might understand better, camera-san.
あ、もっと寄って貰っていいです。あーー！！バイバイ！バイバイ！
Ah, you can come closer. Ahh!! Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
ま、可愛いからいっか！ありがとう。今のいっしゅんのね、あのこれをね、スクショしてもらえたかも知れないですね。
Well, it's cute so it's fine! Thank you. You might have gotten a screenshot!
ダメダメ、ダメダメ！
No way, no way!
はい。でも今日はね、パトラお姉さんとやりたいこといっぱいあります、もう。
Yes. But today, there are so many things we want to do with Patra-neesan.
何をやするのかな？何をやするのかな？ライブとかしたいし！
What are we going to do? We want to do a live or something!
素敵なASMRも聞いてみたいし、ま、とにかくたくさんのことやりたいね！
We want to hear wonderful ASMR too, and do lots of things!
どこから始まればいいかな、もこちゃん？まずは一緒にポップトーク？
Where should we start, Mococo? First, pop talk together?
ふたりで。そうね、しかもASMRで、お耳と。
The two of us. That's right, in ASMR, with ears.
えと、ポップトークって、あの、えっとどんな？
Um, pop talk, like, what kind?
あの、もしもしモコちゃんがすごく元気にする言葉をいつもやってる感じで、いつもふ
Like Mococo always making super energetic words, always...
モーニングの水曜日の
Good morning! It's Wednesday, so...
そうだ。えっと、みんなのこころ励ますような、えっと、パプトクやってるんですけど、
you know, we're doing a "Puff Talk" to cheer everyone's heart up!
そうなんだよね、ちょっと。
That's right. You know, um...
今日は、えっと、今日は、みんなの、お耳、元気がないかなあって思ってて。
today, um, we thought everyone's ears might be feeling a little tired.
モコちゃん、モコちゃん、
Mococo, Mococo,
小さくてかわいいね。
you're so small and cute!
小さくないよ！
I'm not small!
そうね。そんな、そんな激しいのは、やめてよね。そんなのじゃないと。
That's right. Hey, don't do something that intense! Not like that!
ちょっとさ、二人さ、後ろ向いて、ちょっとふりふりしてよ。
Hey, you two, turn around and shake your tails a bit!
かわいい！あっ、かわいい！あっ、ご褒美！
Cute! Ah, so cute! Ah, a reward!
大きいの？でも、これは、ぱっぷとく、関係ないですね、関係ないです。
Is it big? But this has nothing to do with "Puff Talk," right? It has nothing to do with it.
ごめん、ごめん、立て札になっちゃうかも。ごめん、なんか、廃品なの忘れててさ。
Sorry, sorry. It might become a signboard. Sorry, I forgot it was junk.
かわいい！モコちゃんの尻尾あるよ。小さいですね。小さいよね。
Cute! Mococo has a tail! It's so small! It really is small!
そう、全然ふわふわモコモコしてない！パットパットしてる！パットパットしてる！かわいい！
Yeah, it's not fluffy and mococo at all! It's puffy-puffy! It's puffy-puffy, cute!
え、今みたいに励ましてくれるってこと？わあ！
Eh, you mean you'll cheer us up like just now?! Wow!
いやあ、楽しみだなあ。ぱんぱお！
Man, I'm looking forward to it. Pampao!
そうね。そうね。だけど、やっぱりみんなの元気、お耳が元気ないのかなって。
That's right. That's right. But still, I wonder if everyone's ears are feeling a bit low on energy.
みんなのお耳が元気ないの？えっ？なんで？えっ？
Everyone's ears have no energy? Eh? Why? Eh?
え、パトラはさっきの尻尾を、お尻ふりふりで元気いっぱいだよ！
Eh, Patra is full of energy with that tail-wagging from earlier!
だけど、ニャイは、どうかな？
But I wonder about Nyai?
耳、友達の、あの神ミミちゃんが最近落ち込んでるから、みんなも元気が足りないはずなの。
Ears... Your friend Kami-mimi-chan has been feeling down lately, so everyone probably lacks energy too.
友達の神ミミっちゃ、あっ、新しいええのの、違う、違う、あ、違うの。違うね。
Your friend Kami-mimi-cha— Ah, a new EE-N-NO— No, no, ah, that's wrong. That's right.
そうね。この神ミミちゃんは、この耳をのぞくと、見えるから。えっ？とりあえず見に行ってみましょう。
That's right. If you peek into this ear of Kami-mimi-chan, you can see inside. Eh? Let's go check it out for now.
えっ、さっき？みせまして。神ミミちゃん？おっ、おっ、おっ、いるかな？
Eh, just now? Let's take a look. Kami-mimi-chan? Oh, oh, oh, is she here?
ははろー！おっけー！
Haharo! Okay!
わーい！すごい！
Yay! Amazing!
おっきい！やったー！わーい！
It's huge! Yay! Hooray!
え、ちょ、ちょ、なんですか？なんか神々しい何かが浮いてますけど、あれは何？立派！野号さんの耳？
Eh, wait, wait, what is this? Something divine is floating there, what is that? Magnificent! Yagoo's ear?
これが神ミミちゃんなんですね。
So this is Kami-mimi-chan.
これが神ミミちゃんだ。やっぱり元気なさそうだな。
This is Kami-mimi-chan. She really looks like she lacks energy.
ええ、野号さんの耳じゃない。あ、ね、スッチーじゃない。
Eh? It's not Yagoo's ear. Ah, right, it's not Suchii.
神ミミちゃん、なんか仕事を選んだほうがいいよって言おうとして。
Kami-mimi-chan, I was about to say you should choose your jobs better.
あ、なるほどね。
Ah, I see.
え、1ミリもわかんないんだけど、あの耳が、ええと、神ミミちゃんで、大きな神ミミちゃんじゃなくて、
Eh, I don't get it at all, but that ear is, um, Kami-mimi-chan... not the big Kami-mimi-chan, but...
お耳の神様で、そう、神ミミちゃんを元気にするの？
The ear god... yes, you're going to cheer Kami-mimi-chan up?
そう！そう、さすがパトラちゃんね。ありがとう、ありがとう、ありがとう。
Yes! Yes, as expected of Patra-chan. Thank you, thank you, thank you!
お前、スマイル。え、パプトク始めていきましょうか！
You, smile. Eh, let's start Puff Talk!
はい、じゃあ、最初は、モコちゃん、やってみて。そう、ちょっとお耳本見せますね。
Okay, then first, Mococo, give it a try. Yes, let's show the ear book a bit.
じゃあ、モコちゃん、準備いいですか？大丈夫？オッケー！それでは、モコちゃんのASMRパプトク！
So, Mococo, are you ready? Is it okay? Okay! Then, Mococo's ASMR Puff Talk!
パパ！パパ！オッケー！じゃあ！
Papa! Papa! Okay! Then!
モコちゃん、準備いいかな？準備！大丈夫だからね。ちょっと
Mococo, are you ready? Ready! It's going to be okay. Just a...
The first ASMR Puff Talk!
あ、モコちゃん、バイノーラルマイクだから。
Ah, Mococo, it's a binaural microphone, so...
はい、パプトク。モコはいつも元気だからね、いつも元気だから。
Yes, Puff Talk. Mococo is always energetic, always energetic.
今日はね、ささやきをボイスでがんばるよ、がんばる。
Today, I'll do my best with whispering voice, I'll do my best.
パパ、じゃあモコちゃん、準備大丈夫だったら、
Papa, so Mococo, if you're ready and okay...
がんばってね。オッケー。
Do your best. Okay.
じゃあ、それでは、モコちゃんのASMRパプトク、スタート！
So then, Mococo's ASMR Puff Talk, start!
Ruffians, it's time.
時が来たぞ！
The time has come!
It's time for a Mococo Puff Talk! Puff Talkの時間だよ。
It's time for a Mococo Puff Talk! It's time for Puff Talk.
Are you going to hear it from me? Mococo!
Ruffians, Ruffians, I know...
I know that you're always doing your best. They ain't out. You can hide it from me.
毎日毎日頑張ってる君はえらいよ！
You're amazing for working hard every single day!
I know it can be rough, and sometimes you feel like no one notices, no one appreciates your efforts. What? Don't worry.
ビデオ！アイデオ！
Video! Audio!
は、時々大変だと思うけど、モココはどれほど頑張ってるの、知ってるよ！
Ah, I think it can be tough sometimes, but Mococo knows how hard you're trying!
And in the end,
the most important thing is to make sure that you do it for yourself, okay?
So that you'll be...
And make sure that you listen to your body when it tells you to take a break, okay?
頑張るのはいいけど
休む時はちゃんと休んでね？うん。
You can do it!
I believe in you!
頑張ってね！
頑張れー！
あーあー
どうかな？
頑張れ頑張れ！聞こえる？聞こえる？
そうそう！聞こえたかな？
神耳ちゃん緊張する！
緊張しますよ、そりゃね。うん。
なんか、なんかやりそうになってきた？
なんか、泣いてる？泣いてる？泣いちゃってる？
泣いてないって！じゃあ神耳ちゃんも元気でたかな？
あれ、神耳ちゃんの事忘れたわ。えっと。
これ言っちゃったよね？パットラーに行ったらじゃなくて神耳か。
そうね、神耳、神耳、うんうんうん。
神耳ちゃん元気でた？
元気？
あー、だからね、はっ！
なんかね、すごく元気そうに...うわあ！
なんか出産して！泣いてる！出産してる！
泣いてるよ！出産してるよ！出産してるって！
出産してるって！おめでとう！いい子！おめでとう！おめでとう！
おめでとう！おめでとう！よかったね！わあー！そう！すごい！えらい！
まさか...まさか。
ホロライブスタジオで出産を見るとは思わなかったよ。えー！
どこ、あれは喜んでるの？
あ、喜んでると思う、ね。
だけどさ、もっともっと...
あの耳を元気にして、さらに神耳ちゃんを喜ばせることが出来るはず！
そう！なるほどね。
ほら、パットラーね、もっと声が聴きたいです！
あ、わかりました！じゃあ、神耳ちゃんを元気にするために頑張ります！
はい！励ませばいいんだよね？
そうそう、なんか、思いっきり気持ち入れたら、あ、気持ちを入れて。
そうそうそう。なんかね、叩いてもなんか元気そうな感じだったよ。神耳ちゃん。
じゃあ叩いちゃダメ？あ、叩いちゃダメ。優しく、優しく。オッケーオッケーオッケー。盛り上がります。
じゃあ、パットラーネさんのポップトークまで３、２、１！
神耳ちゃん？神耳ちゃん、どうしたの？
何か辛いことがあったのかな？癒し、癒し、癒し、癒し。
いいか、いいか。いいか、いいか。さっきは一杯頑張ったね。
出産おめでとう。ずっと味方だから安心してね。
You are doing great just by being alive.
Fight!
Fightはあれか、戦う方か。よかった！やったぜ！
出産おめでとうって、そこまで言うんですか、パットラーネ。
出産おめでとう。やっぱ今の話は神耳ちゃんを元気したらいいかなっていうからさ。そう、あってるかな？
そうそうそうそう。そっか！神耳ちゃんもっと元気出そうかな？うん、じゃあ、パットラーネのポップトーク。
オッケー！オッケー！すごーい！頑張れー！
じゃあ、まだ神耳ちゃんもっと元気出そうかな？うん、じゃあ、パットラーネのポップトーク。オッケーオッケー。
ポップトーク？うん。
また産んでる！産んでる！元気だな！すごい！神耳ちゃん。何耳びき？
そういう数え方だよね。どうやって耳数えるか。神耳お腹いっぱい。ね、もう十分元気なような気もするけどね。
じゃあパットラーネもやってみよう！ポップトークやってみますね。オッケー！はい！ほら！頑張ってね。楽しい。
パットラーネのポップトーク。オッケー、準備大丈夫かな？
オッケー、それではパットラーネのASMRポップトークスタートです！
季節も変わってきて、ちょっと寒くなれてきてるね。
あんまり無理しないでね。スプリンクラーがもっとクールだよ、ほら。
無理しないでね。
Please don't overdo it.
体調崩したらね、
If you ruin your health,
ふわわ心配になるから。
Fuwawa will get worried, you know.
ぱうぱう、Please make sure you get lots of vitamins.
Paupau! Please make sure you get lots of vitamins.
Don't get sick! You have to eat more than just donuts, okay?
ぱうぱう、お元気でねえ
Paupau, stay healthy!
うわーい！わーい！わーい！
Yay! Yay! Yay!
ぱうぱう！気持ちはとっても嬉しかった！
Paupau! We were so happy!
じゃあ、かみみちゃんどうだったかな？
So, how was it, Kamimi-chan?
うん…かみみちゃんもね、すっそういろいりがんばってるから
Yeah, Kamimi-chan is working hard on various things, so
ドーナツばっかり食べないほうがいいです。食べれる口あるのかな？
You shouldn't just eat donuts. Do you even have a mouth to eat them?
やきっとな…ドーナツはうそっから入るじゃないかな？
Probably... donuts enter from the ears, right?
なんてまりだね、かみみちゃんはね。もっともっと元気が出そうかな？
What a unique style, Kamimi-chan. Will that give you even more energy?
じゃあもっと元気になるために、ストロレイちゃんの大好きなあれやりましょう！
So to get even more energy, let's do Stroraychan's favorite thing!
え、なに？一緒に温泉入ってくれるの？
Eh, what? You'll take a bath with me?
アイスかいぶつ？いや、ちょっとちがいも…
Ice monster? Wait, that's different...
まるはね、ふぶき先輩とあれと一緒にやりたいな。
Well, I want to do that with Fubuki-senpai together.
じゃあ楽しみにしてるね！待ってて！
Then I'm looking forward to it! Wait for me!
じゃあラフィーアンズとわんちゃんこちらへどうぞ！
Now, Lowfians and doggies, please come this way!
え、ふぶきちゃんとやったって、カニプ食べたりとか、あと、あ、そうそうあの紐、あちがう、えっと、み、でっかい耳をね、なんか割って遊ぶとか、
Eh, you did it with Fubuki-chan, like eating crab, or... oh right, that string, no, um, playing with breaking big ears...
あ、そうた、せっかくね、このね、マロのお店のスタジオにいるんで、ちょっとやりたいことあるんで、いいですか？
Oh, that's right! Since we're in Maro's store studio, there's something I want to do, is that okay?
ラフィーアンズ刺激が強かったらごめんね。ほーれ、ほーれ、ほーれ、ほーれ。今日はふわもこの淫声まろを聞きなさい。
Sorry if the Lowfians' stimulation was too strong. Here, here, here, here. Today, listen to Fuwamoco's lewd Maro voice!
とらわれるとなにやるんですか？たくさん！たくさん聞いてね！
What do you do when you're caught? Listen a lot, a lot!
うおおお！あ、ふわふわふわふわ、あ、指できちゃった！じゃーん、できまーした！
Uooo! Ah, fluffy fluffy, ah, fingers are done! Ta-da, we did it!
あ、見て見て！お耳がいっぱい！うわすごーい。これなくなってなかったんかよ。
Ah, look look! So many ears! Wow, amazing. Weren't these supposed to be gone?
うわ、うそっ！ふぶき先輩とやったんじゃないですか。そう、ふぶきちゃんとね、退治したはずなんだけどね。復活しちゃったかな？
Whoa, no way! Didn't you defeat them with Fubuki-senpai? Yeah, we should have defeated them with Fubuki-senpai. Did they revive?
しました！しました！ええとこれは一応何なのかな。そう。じゃあこれはね
We did! We did! Um, what is this supposed to be anyway? Yeah. So this is...
あ、ふわわ行けますよ。おうおう！
Ah, Fuwawa can go! O-oh!
次はお耳割り選手権！
Next is the Ear Breaking Championship!
え、お耳割り選手権とは？
Eh, what is the Ear Breaking Championship?
うん、たぶんね、みんな知らないと思う。月曜なんだよね。初めてします。
Yeah, I think nobody knows. It's Monday. This is our first time doing it.
こちらのASMRお耳割り選手権ですが、ランダムに選ばれるテーマに沿ったASMRボイスで、あの耳たちを何枚割れるのかを競うゲームとなっております。
This ASMR Ear Breaking Championship is a game where you compete to see how many of those ears you can break using ASMR voices tailored to randomly chosen themes.
そうなんだよね。なぜか耳をね、割るっていうよくわからないシステムなんですけど、お耳が喜ぶと割れます。なるほど。
That's right. For some reason, it's a weird system where you break ears, but when the ears are pleased, they break. I see.
そうそうそうそう、テーマに沿った素敵なボイスであればあるほど、あの耳たちが幸せになってたくさん割れまーす！
Exactly, exactly. The more wonderful the voice fitting the theme is, the happier those ears become and the more they break!
いろんなシチュエーションのふわもこが見れるということですね。何枚もね、ありえるので、ちょっとパーフェクト目指してがんばりましょう！
That means you can see Fuwamoco in all sorts of situations. Since there could be many, let's aim for perfection and do our best!
え、待って待って。これ誰が判定するの？いいか悪いか。お耳ちゃんか？じゃあお耳ちゃんが判定するの？お耳ちゃんね、思ったよりデバあるんだな。
Eh, wait wait. Who judges this? Whether it's good or bad. Ear-chan? So Ear-chan judges? Ear-chan has more devices than I thought.
じゃあ早速やります。テーマはどんなテーマを用意してるかちょっと見てみましょうか。
Then let's do it right away. Let's take a look at what kind of themes we have prepared.
ASMRお耳割りテーマ
[ASMR Ear-Breaking Themes]
ドーナツ
Donut...
おもちも？
Mochi too?
うん、ドーナツぱぷ
Yeah, donut pup...
ドーナツともわかるかもしれないね
You might even tell it's a donut.
サイズどうやって食べると...
How to eat the size...
お耳の気持ちとかね、お耳ちゃんの気持ちかな？
Like how the ear feels, or the ear's feeling?
おう！そう！
Right!
ウーレッド...
Roulette...
スタート！
Start!
耳の気持ち！
How does the ear feel?
耳の気持ちなのだ！
It's "How does the ear feel"!
めちゃくちゃ難しそう
That sounds super difficult.
難しいの、劇にする？
Make the difficult one into a play?
お耳の気持ちを考えて、お耳になってくださいね
Think about the ear's feelings and become the ears!
え、それ絶対できる！できる！
We can definitely do it! We can!
自信しかない！
We're nothing but confident!
じゃあ、ふわわの準備...
Well then, Fuwawa's preparation...
心の準備まあるだけど
Heart's preparation is just...
ぱおぱお、オッケー、オッケー！
Pao pao, okay, okay!
じゃあ、お耳の気持ちまで...
Well then, until the feeling of the ears...
3、2、1、どうぞ！
3, 2, 1, go!
ぽかぽか...
Pokapoka...
お耳...今日は...いい気持ちですか？
Ear... are you feeling good today?
どんな気持ちかな？
What kind of feeling is it?
ここ、近づくと...
Here, when we get close...
嬉しい、ハッピー...
Happy, happy...
Does the ear feel happy when it gets close like this?
ぽか、ぽか、ぽか...
Poka, poka, poka...
ぽかぽかぽか！えー！
Pokapokapoka! Eh!
耳の気持ちってどんな気持ち？
What kind of feeling is an ear feeling?
いやでもなんか、ちゃんと...
Well, but somehow, properly...
ふわふわふわふわ...
Fuwafuwafuwafuwa...
え、簡単！可愛い！
Eh, easy! Cute!
耳めっちゃあったぞ今！4枚！わあー！
There were so many ears just now! Four! Wow!
え、フワちゃんもハッピーだった？え、よかったよ！
Eh, was Fuwa-chan happy too? Eh, that was good!
耳は終わってないかもしれないけど、みんなの心が...ぽれちゃってる...
Ears might not be done yet, but everyone's hearts are melting...
あ、そう、ハッピー！ありがとう、お耳ちゃん！いやもう、よかったよ、こまり！
Ah, right, happy! Thank you, o-mimi-chan! Man, that was good, Komari!
特に、なんかさ...
Especially, like...
お耳にね、なんか、あの、こう、語りかけてるの、めっっちゃよかった！
Talking to the ears like that was suuuuper good!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
声の震えがヤバくて！
Your voice was trembling so much!
いいっててた
They said it was good.
そう、心臓の震えが...
Yeah, the heart's trembling...
でも、ここは、その、その震え深みでね、ご褒美みたいなね、感じで！
But here, with that trembling depth, like a reward!
ほら、コメントもすごいですよ！
Look, the comments are amazing too!
今日はもう...
Today...
え、聴こえたって！
Eh, they heard it!
え、聴こえた？そう、震え...震えはまたいいの、って！
Eh, you heard it? Yeah, the trembling is good again, they say!
でしょ、でしょ、でしょ！
Right, right, right!
じゃあ、もうここも頑張ろうかに！
Well then, let's do our best for this one too!
そう！モコちゃんの次はもこちゃんでしょ！
That's right, Moco-chan's next is Moco-chan!
ずるい！
Unfair!
あ、じゃあパトラ、パトラに上手に甘えだできたら、あの、変わってあげるよ！
Well then, Patra, if you can act spoiled well to Patra, um, I'll switch with you!
パトラおねえちゃん、お願いだから...変わって！
Patra big sis, please... switch with me!
え、可愛いー！可愛いけど、モコモコがやりたい！
Eh, so cute! Cute, but Mococo wants to do it!
ずるい！
Unfair!
いや、あめとむちですからね、あめとむち！え、可愛かったなー！
Well, it's carrot and stick, you know, carrot and stick! Eh, it was so cute!
いいよね、いいよね！
Good, right? Good, right?
じゃあ、可愛い...ウーレッド、スタート！
Then, cute... Roureddo, start!
トレイでこい、トレイでこい！
Toilet, come on, toilet!
はずかし寝言
Embarrassing sleep-talking
いや、これは毎日のことじゃないですか？
No, isn't this an everyday thing?
そう、そう。
Yeah, yeah.
え？違いますか？毎日じゃない？
Huh? Isn't it? Not every day?
だって、ねぇ、毎日可愛い寝言言ってるから。
Because, hey, you say cute sleep-talking every day.
おほびー
Oh-ho-bee!
え、なんていうの？
Eh, what do you mean?
あ、普通は、うん、ばっ。
Ah, usually, um... bam!
はっ！ばっ！って。
Ha! Bam!
それ恥ずかしいっていうか、いつもの通りの二人ではあんまり可愛くないから、恥ずかしいですよね。
That's embarrassing, or rather, since the two of us normally aren't that cute, it's embarrassing.
ああ、なるほど。
Ah, I see.
なるほど。ばお。
I see. Bao.
ばお、ばお、ばお。
Bao, bao, bao.
じゃあ、もこちゃんの
Then, Mococo's...
心の準備、いーい？
Mental preparation, rea-dy?
いや、心はもう壊れてるけど、頑張りまーす！
Well, my heart is already broken, but I'll do my best!
ばお、ばお！
Bao, bao!
じゃあ、もこちゃんの恥ずかしい寝言まで、3、2、1！
Then, until Mococo's embarrassing sleep-talking... 3, 2, 1!
どうぞ。
Go ahead.
かわいい
Cute...
はあ
Haah...
ブルーベリー
Blueberry...
どうぞ。
Here you go.
と、ブルーベリー
And... blueberry...
の、の、と、と、今いまいぶるーべりー
No, no, st-st-stop, blueberry...
のい、の、の、すとっぷ
No, no, stop...
うまい、アイスクリーム。
Delicious ice cream.
ちゃんと食べるからね。
I'll eat it properly, okay?
かわいい。
So cute.
おいしい。
Delicious.
ブルーベリー！
Blueberry!
え、すごい、すごい！
Whoa, amazing, amazing!
耳みみ！
Ears, ears!
いや、かわいい！めっちゃ笑ってるじゃん、もこちゃん！
Man, so cute! You're laughing so much, Mococo!
え、ろく？ろく、ろく、ろく！
Eh, six? Six, six, six!
ばお、ばお、ばお！
Bao, bao, bao!
すごい！えっと、最近、え、夢あった？
Amazing! Um, recently, did you have a dream?
なんか、ブルーベリーの夢？え、ブルーベリーの夢じゃなかったけど、え、スバール先輩と、
Like, a blueberry dream? Eh, it wasn't a blueberry dream, but, um, with Subaru-senpai and...
なんかレイ姉の夢を見て、なんかハグして、なんかポルラ姉の髪がすごく柔らかくて、あ、レイ姉今嫉妬してる！
I saw a dream about Rey-ne, and we hugged, and Porla-ne's hair was so soft... Ah, Rey-ne is jealous right now!
ポルラ姉の髪柔らかいもんね。
Porla-ne's hair is really soft, after all.
やっと、しょーしゅ、じゃなくて、しょーしゅじゃあ、手置いて、ふわ、こんな夢見たのって
Finally, "Shoshu," no, "Shoshu," put your hands down... Fuwa, I saw a dream like this!
話したの。そしたらね、なんか寝言も凄かったから。
I talked about it. And you know, her sleep-talking was amazing too.
でも前はブルーベリーだったのに、もこちゃんがブルーベリーの話してた。分かる？
But before it was blueberry, yet Mococo was talking about blueberries. You know?
ブルーベリーの夢見て寝言言ってたってこと？そう。それめっちゃ恥ずかしいよね。
You mean she had a dream about blueberries and talked in her sleep? Yeah. That's super embarrassing, right?
かわいいわ！
So cute!
じゃあ、次！次！
Now, next! Next!
やっと、ましろ姉、ポルラ姉、ポルラ姉、ごめん！
Finally, Mashiro-ne, Porla-ne, Porla-ne, sorry!
びゅんびゅんじゃなくて、ルーフね、ルーフ！
Not byun-byun, roof-ne, roof!
ルータ姉と一緒に揺れたいんだよ、一緒に揺れたい、一緒に揺れたい！
I want to sway together with Ruuta-ne, I want to sway together, I want to sway together!
ジャンプ、ジャンプ、ジャンプ！あ、強せい、ストップ！強制、ストップ！
Jump, jump, jump! Ah, forced stop! Forced stop!
じゃあ、ブルーベリーじゃなくて、ルーレット！ルーレット！
Then, not blueberry, roulette! Roulette!
パトラ姉さ、準備いいですか、ルーレット？いつでもカイン、オッケー！
Patra-ne, are you ready for the roulette? Anytime you want, okay!
ルーレット、スタートン！
Roulette, start-ton!
ストップ！
Stop!
添い寝してくれる保育園の先生！
A preschool teacher lying next to you for a nap!
添い寝してくれる保育園の先生！わあ！
A preschool teacher lying next to you for a nap! Wow!
え、どう？すごい向いてると、あ、向いてる！
Eh, how is it? It really suits you, ah, it suits you!
パトラ姉さん、こういうASMRやったことあるんじゃないですか？
Patra-neesan, haven't you done this kind of ASMR before?
あ、の、ある。なんかママASMRとか。そうそうあるあるあるある。
Ah, um, I have. Like mama ASMR and stuff. Yeah, yeah, there is, there is.
じゃあ、もう自然に出るんですね。おらの夢は全然、はい。
So it just comes out naturally then. My dreams are totally—yes.
じゃあ、コワモコは、みて、いろいろね。喉痛みますね。喉痛みます！
Then, Fuwawa and Mococo, look, various things. Our throats hurt. Our throats hurt!
わあ。つまり、パトラがやったらそれをフワモコがやってくれるってこと？
Wow. So if Patra does it, Fuwawa and Mococo will do it too?
しごくのは、しごくのは、頑張ります！頑張ります！オッケー、うれしい！うん。
We'll do our best! We'll do our best! Okay, yay! Yeah.
じゃあパトラ姉さ、準備いいですか？いつでもカイン、オッケー！
Then Patra-ne, are you ready? Anytime you want, okay!
じゃあ、パトラ姉さんの、え、添い寝の保育園の先生、まで、あ、3、2、1！
Then, Patra-ne's, um, preschool teacher taking a nap with you... until then, ah, 3, 2, 1!
はい、眠くな...
Okay, getting sleepy...
ちょっとかな？
Just a bit?
フワワちゃんとモココちゃんと遊んだから疲れたの？
Are you tired because you played with Fuwawa and Mococo?
よしよし
There, there.
いいこいいこ
Good girl, good girl.
先生が寝るまでトントンしてあげるね
Sensei will gently pat you until you fall asleep.
とんとん、とんとん、とんとん、とんとん
Pat, pat, pat, pat...
こわい夢見たの？
Did you have a scary dream?
大丈夫、大丈夫
It's okay, it's okay.
よしよしよし
There, there, there.
うん、そうなの
Mm, is that so?
じゃあ先生と一緒に寝よっか
Then shall we sleep together with sensei?
はーい、いいこいいこ、先生の胸でおやすみなさい
Okay, good girl, sleep tight on sensei's chest.
あれ？どうしたの？
Huh? What's wrong?
耳だ！耳が！
Ears! The ears!
耳が折れた！
The ears folded!
もしかして…もしかして…
Could it be... Could it be...
あと1個だよ、フワワ！
There's one left, Fuwawa!
すごい！すごい！
Amazing! Amazing!
いやあ、もっと防音力をみせたいなと思いましたね
Well, I thought I wanted to show even more soundproofing power.
すごいでもモコちゃん、やりたくてもそういうの出来ないよね？
Wow, but Mococo, even if you wanted to, you couldn't do that, right?
え、どういう意味？
Eh, what do you mean?
どういう意味だよ、それ！
What do you mean by that?!
いやでもね、モココのね
Well, but, Mococo's...
あの、その、えっと、あの、その、あの、あの、そうね
Um, that, let's see, that, you know...
モココちゃんのその、あ、ちがう、あの、ステキな胸にこうね、ぽんぽんって寝るのもすごくいいと思うんだよね
Mococo-chan's, ah, no, um, wonderful chest, like, pat-pat, sleeping on it is also really good, I think.
ねむ、ねむ、お、モコちゃんもこもこしてるから
Sleepy, sleepy, o, Mococo is fluffy so...
そう、そう、もこもこしてる！ふわふわ！
Yeah, yeah, she's fluffy! Fluffy!
あれね、他のシチュエーションも早く聞きたいんだけどさ、モココ、えっと、モコちゃんと、えっと、ジョキポ、ジョキポ、ジョキポ
Say, I want to hear other situations quickly too, Mococo, um, with Mococo-chan, um, jokipo, jokipo, jokipo...
ジョキポキ、ジョキポキ、みんな、3人で、オッケー
Jokipoki, jokipoki, everyone, three of us, okay?
じゃあ、ジョキポキは、ふもこ、オッケー、やってみて！できなかったらオッケー
Then, jokipoki, Fumoko, okay, try it! If you can't, okay...
ちょっと待って、2回連続
Wait a minute, twice in a row!
コントローラー3台！
Three controllers!
あ、じゃあさ、ちょっとさ
Ah, then, say, a little bit, say...
あの、夢があってさ、あの、フワモコさん、心音サンドイッチって知ってる？
Um, I have a dream, um, Fuwamoco-san, do you know what a heartbeat sandwich is?
最近覚えた日本語、それをさ、ちょっとさ
Japanese I learned recently, so, you know, a bit...
こう、聞きたいんだけどさ、ちょっと、あの、バイノーラルマイクで、ちょっと心音サンドイッチ聞けたらもう一回やりたいなって思うんだよね
I want to hear it like this, um, a bit, with the binaural mic, if I could hear the heartbeat sandwich again, I'd want to do it once more, you know.
うん、あ、ごめん、でも、にがやってる、やっぱりね、視聴者の声に応えるのが一番だと思うんですよね
Yeah, ah, sorry, but, we're doing it, after all, responding to the viewers' voices is the most important thing, I think.
そう、そう、そう、そう、そうだよね！あ、じゃあ、心の、し、し、し、心音サンドイッチ
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right! Ah, then, heart, sh-, sh-, sh-, heartbeat sandwich!
えとね、えとね、ちょっと、あの、この、かわらの、お耳ちゃんね、ちょっと、あの、突き抜けるかもしれないんだけど
Um, you know, um, you know, a bit, um, this tile, ear-chan, you know, a bit, um, might pierce through, but...
こうやって、さあ、あ、ち、も、も、モコちゃんはもっとなんか突くんじると聞こえないかもしれない
Like this, say, ah, ch-, mo-, mo-, Mococo might not hear it if you poke more...
あ、ごめん、フワワは、こういう
Ah, sorry, Fuwawa, like this...
あ、いいですね、おう、な、うん、これで、どくどく聞こえないかな
Ah, this is good, oh, na, un, with this, can you hear the thumping?
パワー、パワー
Power, power!
あ、まだ、こっちは、すごい、ドキドキ
Ah, still, this side is amazing, dokidoki.
ドキドキしてる。もうちょっと上かな？どきどき、どきどき
My heart is beating. A bit higher? Thump thump, thump thump.
モココ、上に上がって、声に
Mococo, move up, to the voice...
あ、聞こえた。は、こわい
Ah, I heard it. Ha, scary.
モココ、薄くて
Mococo, thin...
ちょっと待って
Wait a minute.
パワー、パワー
Power, power!
え、こっちかな？
Eh, is it this way?
え、近い、近いよ
Eh, close, it's close!
心臓のところをこうやっていこう
Let's go like this at the heart.
聞こえないかな？心臓が、心臓がちゃんとドキドキはしてる
Can't you hear it? The heart, the heart is definitely beating.
心臓が聞こえないね、パワー、パワー
Can't hear the heart, power, power!
神耳ちゃんが、でも耳が近いね
Kami-mimi-chan, but the ears are close.
え、なんか、これ神耳ちゃん、これからの課題ってこと？
Eh, like, is this Kami-mimi-chan, a challenge for the future?
これ神耳ちゃんだけに聞こえたの？
Did this only reach Kami-mimi-chan's ears?
神耳ちゃんだけに聞こえたの？
Did it only sound to Kami-mimi-chan?
聞こえた？
Did you hear that?
わぁ！
Yay!
全部割れた！
They all broke!
全部割れたよ！
耳かき、あそこは！
Over there is ear cleaning!
何か聞こえてる？
Can you hear something?
聞こえてるよ！
We can hear it!
よっぱらい！
Drunkards!
ふーみんちゃんの元気が出たってことかな？
I wonder if Fuu-min-chan got her energy back?
ロールケーキサンデー サンドイッチマンデー 気分次第で
Roll cake Sunday, sandwich Monday, whatever you feel like
期待半分 確率イーブン 明日はこれから
Half expectations, even odds, tomorrow starts from now
ネコとか (Ole!) すすきが (Ole!)
Cats (Ole!) and pampas grass (Ole!)
手まねきしてる
are beckoning.
何もない (Ole!?) つまらない (Ole!?)
Say goodbye to nothing (Ole!?) and being bored (Ole!?)
今日はさようなら
today.
まわる まわるっ てく (アイヤイヤ)
Spinning around, going round and round (ai-yai-ya)
やりましょう！
Let's do it!
じゃあ二人でルーレット回そうか！
Then let's have the two of them spin the roulette!
二人が頑張ってくれたからルーレット回そうか！
Since the two of them did their best, let's spin the roulette!
オッケー！
Okay!
ルーレット スタート！
Roulette start!
トイレに行きたくてたまらない時
When you urgently need to go to the bathroom
やるか？
Shall we do it?
心の準備、大丈夫？
Are you mentally prepared?
オッケーです！
Ready!
え、これフワモコちゃんにやってほしいけどね
Well, I'd want Fuwamoko-chan to do this, though.
え、大丈夫？どうどうどう？
Eh, are you okay? How is it?
さあ！
Now!
トイレに行きたくてたまらない時までは…
Until the time when you urgently need to go to the bathroom...
3、2、1！
3, 2, 1!
あの、えっと、あの、えっと…
Um, well, um, well...
あの、えっと、あの、あの
Um, well, um, um...
なんでもないんだけど
It's nothing much, but
ちょっと、あの、配信もうちょっとで終わろっかな
I was thinking of ending the stream a little soon.
え、まだ始めたばっかり？
Eh, we just started?
え、で、でもなんかちょっと
Eh, but, but somehow a little...
え、なんか、うん、うん、なんか、あの、ビショビショになりそうだし
It looks like it's going to get soaking wet, um...
はい、足そう、ちょっと
Yes, let's add some, a little.
はあ、はあ、はあ
Hah, hah, hah...
ちょっと気合入れて
Put in some spirit...
ちょっと、なんかいろいろあの、出そうだから
Um, since a lot of things are about to come out...
えと、う、ん、はあ… ちょっと気合入れて、ちょっと、なんかいろいろあの、出そうだから
Umm, ugh, mm, hah... Put some spirit into it...
う、う、う、あっ、もう動きないかもしれないな
Ugh, ugh, ah, maybe we can't move anymore.
お、あっ、ちょ、ちょ
Woah, ah, wait, wait.
これを… パドラじゃないやつにする？
Shall we make this... something other than Patra?
なににす？
What will it be?
なにが？
What is it?
ワン！バーン！
Wan! Baan!
なになに？
What, what?
え？え？耳かきじゃん！
Eh? Eh? It's ear cleaning!
え？え？違う違う違う！
Eh? Eh? No, no, no!
え？耳かきじゃない？ ちょっと待って！
Eh? Not ear cleaning? Wait a minute!
えっ、なんで割れてるの？
Eh, why are they broken?
耳かきじゃん！
It's ear cleaning!
あれ？
Huh?
あ、そっか。あの、トイレに我慢してる人を…
Ah, I see. Um, people who are holding in going to the bathroom...
初めにやってたんですね
...we did that at the beginning, right?
おーいお料理どうするの？
Hey, what about cooking?
パーン！パーン！怒ってる！
Paan! Paan! They're angry!
怒ってる！へー！
They're angry! Heh!
じゃあ、やっぱり
Well, as expected,
二人同時にあのシチュエーションやってほしいな
I want the two of you to do that situation at the same time.
え、いいよ、いいよ
Eh, sure, sure.
結構、別のシチュエーションなら
Well, if it's a different situation,
あ、別の？ま、しょうがないな。他にもいっぱいあったからね
Ah, a different one? Well, can't be helped. There were lots of others too.
やっぱりね！
As expected!
まだ、あの、トイレのお姉ちゃんとやりたいことがあって
There's still something I want to do with the bathroom big sister,
ちょっと、お願いしたいです
and I'd like to ask you.
もう一回、もう一回、もう一回やりましょうか
Shall we do it one more time, one more time, one more time?
オッケーです！
Okay!
じゃあ、今度はね、フワモコ二人でやってみましょうか
Well, this time, let's have Fuwawa and Mococo try it together.
やった！やった！
Yay! Yay!
本当にトイレ行って
Go to the bathroom for real!
え、トイレ行くの？すぐ帰る？
Eh, going to the bathroom? Coming back right away?
じゃあ、ルーレットもう一回だけ
Then, just one more roulette.
オッケー、じゃあ
Okay, then
ルーレット
Roulette
スタート！
Start!
添い寝してくれる保育園の先生
A preschool teacher lying next to you for a nap
赤ちゃんに生まれ変わった！
I've been reborn as a baby!
赤ちゃんになってぴーぴー！
Becoming a baby, pee pee!
ママだよ！
I'm your mama!
パドラお姉ちゃんは、パドラママになった！
Patra big sis became Patra mama!
イエス！イエス！イエス！
Yes! Yes! Yes!
アイ・アム・ママ！
I am mama!
フワモコ・ベイビー！
Fuwamoko baby!
あ、フワココ！あ、ポココ！
Ah, Fuwakoko! Ah, Pokoko!
イエス、ピーカブー！
Yes, peek-a-boo!
ポンポン・ポコちゃ
Ponpon Poko-cha
フワモコ・ベイビーも頑張りましょう
Fuwamoko babies will do their best too!
え、かわいい！
Eh, cute!
すっごく早く見たいよ、二人の
I want to see the two of them so badly!
おむつかかってるの
Wearing diapers
大丈夫かな？
Will it be okay?
オッケー、頑張ろう！
Okay, let's do our best!
はい、それでわおふたりのパドラの娘で、3、2、1、たんざん！
Yes, then with the two of them as Patra's daughters, 3, 2, 1, tanzan!
はあ、はあ、はあ、こんばんは
Hah, hah, hah, good evening
お腹空いてますよ
I'm hungry
すい、すいてますよ
Hungry, hungry
こんばんは、こんばんは
Good evening, good evening
ぽっぽっぽ、ぽっぽっぽ
Poppoppo, poppoppo
ぽっぽっぽ、ぽっ
Poppoppo, po
ドーナツ、ドーナツ
Donuts, donuts
フワはまだ歯が…
Fuwa still has her teeth...
歯が、やっぱりないけどどうしよう
Her teeth aren't there after all, what should we do?
かわいいけど、どう…
She's cute, but how...
ドーナツ… ドーナツ…
Donuts... Donuts...
食べたいっチュ…
Wanna eatchu...
食べまっチュ！
Gonna eatchu!
かわいい… ドーナツ…
Cute... donuts...
パウパウ… パウパウパウ… ドーナツ…
Paw paw... paw paw paw... donuts...
くださーい！ドーナツ！
Please! Donuts!
すきぴ…
My favorite...
パウパウ…
Paw paw...
いつか僕らの上をスレスレに
通り過ぎていったあの飛行機を
That plane that flew right above our heads
and passed by just a moment ago...
不思議なくらいに覚えてる
I remember it so clearly, strangely enough.
意味もないのに なぜか
For no reason at all, why?
えー、もっと！
Eh, more!
いや、これは…え、これさ、なんか…
No, this is... um, this, like...
3人でもやってみない？
Shouldn't the three of us try it too?
うん、せっかくだからね！
Yeah, since we have the chance!
せっかく寿司ね！
Since it's sushi-ne!
ま、トイレはもうね、バッチリセーフだよね？
Well, the bathroom break is totally safe now, right?
セーフ！
Safe!
また来るかもしれないよ、トイレが！
The bathroom might come again!
じゃ、じゃあ…
Well, well then...
ルレット… ルレット…
Roulette... Roulette...
ルレットが出てこない…
If the roulette doesn't come out...
残酷な運命が決まっているとして
それがいつの日か僕の前に現れるとして
Assuming a cruel fate is predetermined,
assuming it appears before me someday...
ストップ！
Stop!
看護師さん！
A nurse!
声がなりてると…
The voice is ringing...
ナース！そうね、ふあもこね、なりてる！
Nurse! That's right, FUWAMOCO, it's ringing!
そう、ホロじい知恵もあったからさ！
Yeah, since we also had Holoji's wisdom!
だからね、夜勤量あるや、アドエト…
だからゲームとかで、すごく学んでるよ！
So, night shift pay... in games and stuff,
we're learning so much!
ゲームとかで、どんなゲーム？
あと、えっと、ピンクの…
Games and stuff, what kind of game?
And, um, pink...
ピンクのあの注射器の！
That pink syringe one!
注射器、注射器！ピンクの！ピンクの！
Syringe, syringe! Pink! Pink!
じゃあ、三人での看護師さん！
Well then, a three-person nurse!
看護師さん、看護師さん！おっけー！
Nurse, nurse! Okay!
じゃあ、えっと、三人での看護師さん。うん。
Then, um, the three-person nurse. Yeah.
さーん、にー、いー、ち…
Three, two, one...
ぱうぱう… 頭も大丈夫？
Paw paw... Is your head okay?
大丈夫、大丈夫、大丈夫… 痛いですか？
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay... Does it hurt?
パントラねさん、反省、反省するよ。
Pantoranesan, I'll reflect on it, I will.
頭の反省… ああー！
Reflecting on the head... Ahh!
よしよし、頭がやられちゃったんだね。
There, there, your head got hurt, huh.
じゃあ、お注射しようか。ぐさっ、ぐさっ…
Well, shall we give you an injection? Stab, stab...
なんか、心臓が痛いって言ってるみたい。
It seems like they're saying their heart hurts.
パワーマッサージ？ パワーマッサージ引き受けるね！
Power massage? I'll take care of the power massage!
パワー！ パワー！ パワー！
Power! Power! Power!
はい、請求書！
Here, the invoice!
パワー、パワー！…請求書って聞こえたけど！
Power, power!... I heard 'invoice', but!
や、請求書だった！
It was an invoice!
え、これで、もう元気でことかな？
耳鳴りが元気になったね！よかった！
Eh, with this, are they full of energy now?
The ringing in the ears got energetic! Good for you!
請求書って、GTAの…そう、請求書…
なるほどね！そういうことなんですね！
An invoice is from GTA... Yeah, an invoice...
I see! So that's how it is!
なんかちょっとナースの知識が違うような
気もするけど…うん、うん、うん！
It feels like the nurse knowledge is a bit
different, though... yeah, yeah, yeah!
ま、でも！耳割れ選手権はここまでです！
そう、耳鳴りが元気になったね！
Well, but! The ear-splitting championship ends here!
That's right, the ringing got energetic!
でもね、まだまだ全部できてなくて…
But still, it's not all done yet...
まだまだ、やりたいことがあります！
おお、まだある！
There's still something we want to do!
Oh, there's more!
今回はお願いしていいですか？うん！
Can we ask you this time? Yeah!
お姉ちゃん大丈夫かな？
いや、違う、違う、違う！一人ばい、スタイルの…
Is big sis okay? No, wait, wait!
Single style...
おねえちゃんで！はい！
With big sis! Yes!
もちろん、もちろん！パワー、パワー！
わー、びっくりした！すごい！
Of course, of course! Power, power!
Wow, I was surprised! Amazing!
じゃあ、ステージの方へ行ってみましょう！
いっせーのーで！
Well, let's head towards the stage!
Ready, set, go!
さあ、今日もみんなで元気に、日本語を覚えていこう！
"Now, let's all happily learn Japanese today too!"
あいうえお かきくけこ さしすせそ
A-I-U-E-O, Ka-Ki-Ku-Ke-Ko, Sa-Shi-Su-Se-So
うー、まだまだ！ たちつてと
Ooh, not yet! Ta-Chi-Tsu-Te-To
なにぬねの はひふへほ
Na-Ni-Nu-Ne-No, Ha-Hi-Fu-He-Ho
うー、もういっちょ！
Ooh, once more!
まみむめも やいゆえよ
Ma-Mi-Mu-Me-Mo, Ya-I-Yu-E-Yo
らりるれろ わをん！
Ra-Ri-Ru-Re-Ro, Wa-Wo-N!
まずは日本語の挨拶！おはようございます、いただきます、ごちそうさまです、いってらっしゃい、いってきます、ありがとうございます！
First, Japanese greetings! Good morning, enjoy your meal, thank you for the meal, have a safe trip, I'm heading out, thank you very much!
こんにちは、お疲れ様です、ごめんなさい、すみません、失礼しました、ありがとうございます！
Hello, good job, I'm sorry, excuse me, pardon me, thank you very much!
こんばんは、お久しぶりです、よろしく、かしこまりました、ありがとうございます！
Good evening, long time no see, nice to meet you, understood, thank you very much!
ただいま、おかえり、おやすみなさい！
I'm home, welcome back, good night!
自分を呼ぶとき どの言葉使うの？
When you refer to yourself, which word do you use?
私、僕、俺、おいら、おいどん…
Watashi, boku, ore, oira, oidon...
「おいどん使ってる奴聞いたことなーい！」
"I've never heard anyone use 'oidon'!"
覚えよう日本語！ GO! 日本語！ GO!
Let's learn Japanese! GO! Japanese! GO!
さあみんなで 覚えよう日本語！ GO!
Come on everyone, let's learn Japanese! GO!
日本語！ GO! 日本語！ GO!
Japanese! GO! Japanese! GO!
声合わせて 50個の音から 溢れ出す想い
Voices aligned, feelings overflowing from 50 sounds
さあ 口ずさめ このメロディ
Come on, hum along to this melody
あいうえお かきくけこ さしすせそ
A-I-U-E-O, Ka-Ki-Ku-Ke-Ko, Sa-Shi-Su-Se-So
うー、まだまだ！ たちつてと
Ooh, not yet! Ta-Chi-Tsu-Te-To
なにぬねの はひふへほ
Na-Ni-Nu-Ne-No, Ha-Hi-Fu-He-Ho
うー、もういっちょ！
Ooh, once more!
まみむめも やいゆえよ
Ma-Mi-Mu-Me-Mo, Ya-I-Yu-E-Yo
らりるれろ わをん！
Ra-Ri-Ru-Re-Ro, Wa-Wo-N!
喜怒哀楽の擬音！
Onomatopoeia for joy, anger, sorrow, and pleasure!
うきうき ほくほく るんるん らんらん
Ukiuki, hokuhoku, runrun, ranran
くすくす にかにた にこりこ
Kusukusu, niania, nitanita, nikoriko
いらいら ぽんぽん むかむか かんかん
Iraira, ponpon, mukamuka, kankan
かりかり ぷりぷり ぷぷぷのぷー がみがみ
Karikari, puripuri, pupupunopuu, gamigami
しくしく めそめそ うるうる ぽろぽろ
Shikushiku, mesomeso, uruuru, poroporo
くすくす おいいおー ひいひい わーわー もずもず うずうず
Kusukusu, oioio, hiihii, waawaa, mozumozu, uzuuzu
ドキドキ ワクワク
Dokidoki, wakuwaku
謝るときさえ テンションが難しい
Even when apologizing, keeping the right tension is hard
ごめんね、すみません、I'm sorry... sorry...
Gomen ne, sumimasen, I'm sorry... sorry...
「最後それ英語じゃん！」
"That last one is English!"
覚えよう日本語！ GO! 日本語！ GO!
Let's learn Japanese! GO! Japanese! GO!
さあみんなで 覚えよう日本語！ GO!
Come on everyone, let's learn Japanese! GO!
日本語！ GO! 日本語！ GO!
Japanese! GO! Japanese! GO!
声合わせて つまづくこともあるけど 気にすることは無い
Voices aligned, even if you stumble, there's nothing to worry about
さあ 胸張って あいうえお！
Come on, puff out your chest, A-I-U-E-O!
「次う ちょっと難しいけど、濁音と半濁音も覚えていこう！」
"Next is a little difficult, but let's also learn voiced and semi-voiced sounds!"
がぎぐげご ざじずぜぞ だぢづでど
Ga-Gi-Gu-Ge-Go, Za-Ji-Zu-Ze-Zo, Da-Ji-Zu-De-Do
ばびぶべぼ ぱぴぷぺぽ
Ba-Bi-Bu-Be-Bo, Pa-Pi-Pu-Pe-Po
ぽ！ ぽぽぽぽぽ！
Po! Popopopopo!
覚えよう日本語！ GO! 日本語！ GO!
Let's learn Japanese! GO! Japanese! GO!
さあみんなで 覚えよう日本語！ GO!
Come on everyone, let's learn Japanese! GO!
日本語！ GO! 日本語！ GO!
Japanese! GO! Japanese! GO!
覚えよう日本語！ GO! 日本語！ GO! さあみんなで 覚えよう日本語！ GO! 日本語！ GO!
Let's learn Japanese! GO! Japanese! GO! Come on everyone, let's learn Japanese! GO! Japanese! GO!
声合わせて 日本語！ GO!
Voices aligned, Japanese! GO!
50個の音から 溢れ出す想い さあ 口ずさめ このメロディ
Feelings overflowing from 50 sounds, come on, hum along to this melody
あいうえお かきくけこ さしすせそ
A-I-U-E-O, Ka-Ki-Ku-Ke-Ko, Sa-Shi-Su-Se-So
うー、まだまだ！ たちつてと
Ooh, not yet! Ta-Chi-Tsu-Te-To
なにぬねの はひふへほ
Na-Ni-Nu-Ne-No, Ha-Hi-Fu-He-Ho
うー、もういっちょ！
Ooh, once more!
まみむめも やいゆえよ
Ma-Mi-Mu-Me-Mo, Ya-I-Yu-E-Yo
らりるれろ わをん！ わおーん！
Ra-Ri-Ru-Re-Ro, Wa-Wo-N! Waoon!
ありがとうございまーす！
Thank you very much!
ありがとう！ありがとうございます！
Thank you! Thank you very much!
ということでね、こうして踊って、
So, dancing like this,
パトラと歌って踊って、
singing and dancing with Patra,
フワモコのね、もう、今日という……。
for Fuwawa and Mococo, today's...
トリビュート！
Tribute!
うれしー！うれしい！
I'm so happy! So happy!
すごくすごくうれしいだって！
I'm so, so happy!
こちらこそありがとう！
Thank you so much to you too!
もう、なんかコメントではね、あの「今日、教育番組」とか
Already, in the comments, things like "Today is an educational program" or...
そうね！
That's right!
そう、なんかすごくすごく楽しい曲だし、そう、そう、
Yes, it's such a fun song, yes, yes,
ポポポポポポー！うれしー！
po-po-po-po-po-po! I'm so happy!
ポポポポポカ！そう、だから楽しかったです！
Po-po-po-po-poka! Yes, so we had a lot of fun!
はい！
Yes!
今回のね、3Dコラボのきっかけとなったパトラお姉様、パトラ！
Patra-onesama, who became the catalyst for this 3D collaboration, Patra!
スカイトラ！うれしー！
Skypatra! I'm so happy!
そう、かわいい！かわいいがいんだよ！
Yes, so cute! It's full of cuteness!
そうだよ！
That's right!
そして、今回のプロデュースのフワモコASMRマイボイスは、本日発売となりましたので、
And now, as for the long-awaited Fuwawa & Mococo ASMR My Voice produced by us, it went on sale today,
改めてお知らせさせてください！
so please let us announce it once again!
ぜひ！
Please!
パトラお姉様プロデュース！フワモコのいる日常、
Produced by Patra-onesama! "Everyday Life with Fuwawa & Mococo"
4つのシチュエーションボイスの発売となりました！
featuring 4 situational voice packs has been released!
日本語バージョンと英語バージョンがありますので、お好みのものをお選びください！
There are Japanese and English versions available, so please choose your favorite!
そして英語！そう！フワモコ！フワモコ！うれしいじゃん、うれしいじゃん！
And English! Yes! Fuwawa and Mococo! Fuwawa and Mococo! We're so happy!
Produce by Patra-neesan! うれしい、うれしい！
Produced by Patra-neesan! So happy, so happy!
And whatever there is four different versions that you can choose from. And we have not only the Japanese version, but also the English version!
And remember, there are four different versions that you can choose from! And we have not only the Japanese version, but also the English version!
なんかね、すでにね、あの、もう聞いたよっていうね、声もね、あってね、
Already, you know, we've gotten voices saying "I've already listened to it!",
発売していて、もう、なんかポップにもね、あの2人のそのジャケットとか
and since it's on sale, on the pop displays, with the jacket of the two of them,
パトラがね「私が作りました」みたいな感じでさ、ちょっと表示してくれて、それがね、うれしかった……！
and Patra like "I made this!" displayed in a farmer-like way, that made us so happy...!
パトラお姉さんのおかげです！ありがとうございます！おめでとう！
It's all thanks to Patra-onesama! Thank you! Congratulations!
でね、そうなの！こだわりポイントっていうのがね、本当全部で、両耳からの2人の息がかかったりとか、
And you know, the attention to detail in total is experiencing their breath in both ears,
バウバウ攻撃もあるけど、なんか、ちょうど、あの、妹っぽくね、
and there are bow-wow attacks, but also acting like a little sister,
あの、ブリードブラザーとか、甘えてくれたり、
or acting spoiled like a sweet brother,
まあ、あと、お姉ちゃんよしよしみたいな、そうそう母性で包み込まれるっていうのね、あの、そう、ね、それぞれの個性も、
and head-pats from an older sister, being enveloped in motherhood, and how each of their personalities...
2人が頑張ってしてくれたから、もうとにかく聞いてくださいっていう感じです！
the two of them worked hard to express, so basically just please listen to it!
でも、お、こだわりもあるっていうお話でね、こだわり、なんだ？さらにね、フルセットでご購入いただけると、
But you know, talking about how there's attention to detail, what is it? Furthermore, if you purchase the full set,
特典が、あります！
there are special bonuses!
まずね、こちらのPC壁紙です！
First, we have these PC wallpapers!
それで、if you buy the full set, you can also get this special bonus here, this PC wallpaper.
And if you buy the full set, you can also get this special bonus here, this PC wallpaper.
フワワもちょっとね、肩出してみました！大人！
Fuwawa bared her shoulders a bit too! So grown-up!
え、モコモコも大胆！え、モコモコいつもおなか出してるじゃないですか？でも今回は脇！
Eh, Mococo is daring too! Eh, doesn't Mococo always show her belly? But this time it's her armpits!
あ、そう、そういえばおなかといえばね、いつも出してるから、ちょっとね、あの、ASMRの音声でちょっとおなかにこうね、あの、ラフィアンが向いたときに、息がね、モコちゃんのおなかに息が当たって、くすぐったいみたいなのもあるのでね、聞いてください！聞いてください！
Ah, right, speaking of bellies, since she always shows it, when the ruffian turns toward the stomach in the ASMR audio, the breath hits Mococo's stomach, making it ticklish, so please listen to that too! Please listen!
そう、そしてカフェラテもあって、
Yes, and there's also caffe latte,
アフタートークボイスもついてきます！そう、そのね、お話そしてもらったボイスになっていまーす！
and the after-talk voice! Yes, it's a voice where we got to chat!
気になる方はフルセットでお願いします！そうなんです、
So if you're curious, please get the full set! That's right,
こうやってね、汗だくの2人に囲まれながら、ちょっとね、すごいボイス取りましたよね！
being surrounded by the two sweating girls like this, we recorded an amazing voice!
ドキドキしちゃう！
It makes my heart race!
しかも、スペシャルボイス
And this is a special voice...
フワワとモココのね、アフターボイス！
After Talk voice featuring Fuwawa and Mococo!
しかも、どちらのボイスも日本語ボイスと英語ボイスの
Also, both Japanese and English versions
両方の音声セットとどちらも同じコンテンツがついてきますので、ご安心くださいね！
are included as separate voice sets with the exact same content, so please rest assured!
日本語と英語が両方やるってなんだかすっごいね？
Doing both Japanese and English is pretty amazing, right?
頑張りました！頑張りました、ほんとに！
We worked hard! We really did!
いや、本当にね、なんだろう、もうあの、ね、朝から晩まで頑張って
Yeah, really, you know, from morning till night, we worked hard
作ったからね！
and created it!
そう、ぜひ聞いてほしいですね！
Yeah, we definitely want you to listen to it!
そう、ぜひ！
Yes, please!
ホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップで
Get yours at the hololive production Official Shop
ゲットしてください！ゲットしてね、ゲットしてね！
please! Get it, get it!
ホロライブオフィシャルショップ！
hololive Official Shop!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you very much!
お願いします！がんばったよ！
Please! We did our best!
そしてそして、なんと、なんと！
And then, and then, guess what, guess what!
ボイスを聞いたほろーみんからベビーも届いています！
We've also received reviews from holomins who listened to the voice!
聞こえちゃったってこと？
You mean you heard it?
感しちゃったね。
You felt it, huh.
ありがとう、ありがとう！
Thank you, thank you!
え、誰だと思う？
Eh, who do you think it is?
え、一番消えてったらフワモコしちゃうのも、多分今はフブキ先輩なんじゃないかな、フブキ先輩のASMR聞いたから。
Eh, if the first one to disappear is Fuwamoco, it's probably Fubuki-senpai right now, because she listened to Fubuki-senpai's ASMR.
なるほどなるほど！フワモコ今言わないかな？フワモコ！
I see, I see! Wouldn't Fuwamoco say that now? Fuwamoco!
じゃあそんなフブキちゃんからのレビューが届いています！ご紹介します！
Now, we've received a review from Fubuki-chan! Let me introduce it!
地獄です 両耳カリカリされながらBAUBAUされている
"It is hell. While having both ears nibbled on, being BAUBAU'd..."
天国の様に感じるかもしれないがこれは意味で地獄です！！
"...you might feel like you're in heaven, but in a sense, this is hell!!"
こんなの耐えられないですよ！！フワモコに両耳をBAUBAUされてる
"There's no way you can endure this!! Having both ears BAUBAU'd by Fuwamoco..."
俺が…フワモコのご主人だ！！気がつけばこうなっているはず
"...I am... Fuwamoco's master!! Before you know it, you'll end up like this..."
既に上に浮きそうになっている…Big☆DREAM
"...already looking like you're floating up... Big☆DREAM"
皆もこちら側へ来ないか…待ってる。だそうです！
"Won't you come to this side too... I'm waiting." So it says!
え！？地獄です！？こんなの耐えられないぜよー！
Eh!? It's hell!? You can't endure this!
フワモコに両耳をBAUBAUされてる俺が俺？俺が俺だった？
"I'm the one having my ears BAUBAU'd by Fuwamoco, me? I was me?"
フワモコの…ご主人だー！
"Fuwamoco's... master!"
マストハブふぶきー！
Must-have Fubuki!
気づけばみんなこうなっているはず！既にマスターフブキはそうなっている！ビッグドリーム！
"Before you know it, everyone should be like this! Master Fubuki is already like that!" Big Dream!
みんなも、みんなもみんなもこちらへ来ないか？待ってます。だそうです。
"Won't you all come over here too? I'm waiting." It says.
なんかすごいね。やっぱり、あの、天国という表現よりも地獄っていう表現が、なんかこうジェットコースターのように表現されてさすがフブキさんです！
That's amazing. As expected of Fubuki-san, expressing it more like a roller coaster, where "hell" rather than "heaven" is expressed!
いやだからうれしいけど、難しい難しいねー！
Yeah, so I'm happy, but it's difficult, difficult!
聞いてるって、そりゃそうだ！何も知らないすこだもんね！
She listened, of course! She's a suzora who knows nothing!
よで、よで、よで、フブキちゃんも聞いてね！うわあって心が、心がすごいことになってるの！
Fubuki-chan, listen too! Wow, my heart, my heart is going through something amazing!
ありがとう！フブキ先輩！だって、こうしちゃったのに、ねえ？
Thank you! Fubuki-senpai! Because you did this, right?
じゃあね、実はね、まだまだ！まだあります！
Well, actually, there's still more! There's still more!
え、誰だと思う？どうなんだろう？
Eh, who do you think it is? I wonder who?
まさか、ピブイちゃんとかじゃないよね？じゃないよね？じゃないよね？そうだよね？じゃないよね？いや、実はこんな方にいただいています！
It couldn't be Pibu-i-chan or someone, right? Not right? Right? Actually, we received it from this person!
こよちゃんですー！
Koyo-chan!
大丈夫かな？こよちゃん、レビューありがとうございます！ではでは
Is she okay? Koyo-chan, thank you for the review! Now then,
フワモコちゃんに両耳から話しかけられたいという夢が叶ったー！！！！！！
"My dream of being spoken to by Fuwamoco-chan from both ears came trueー!!!!!!"
両耳ぷーらは至福です…
"Two-ear pura is bliss..."
キラキラキラキラ！
Sparkling sparkling!
モコちゃんの膝枕ボイスは「お兄ちゃん」呼びに悶えられるし、
"Mococo's lap pillow voice makes you writhe from being called 'Onii-chan'..."
ちょっといってくる無邪気で生意気な感から、そ、そんなことまで…！？と悶絶の流れ。
"...from the innocent and cheeky vibe, and leading to writhing with 'Th-that far...!?', a torrent of agony."
最高に可愛かったです、ごちそうさまでした！！！
"It was supremely cute, thank you for the meal!!!"
両項の流れ、ちょっと、こういう時にだけ頭使わないで！
"Ryou-kou's flow... hey, don't use your head only at times like this!"
えーっと、たぶんすごく、えーと、いいってことかな？
Ah, wait... so...
ふわわ、何？
Fuwawa, what?
えーっと、えー、えーっと、ちょ、待っ……、ん、く。
So, um, um, um, wait, wait.
これね、わかりやすく！わかりやすく！
Let's make it easy to understand!
え、最高に可愛かったです！お疲れ様でしたー！
It was super cute! Thank you so much!
パトラさん！
Patra-san!
パトラゼロです！
Zero day!
頂いちゃったね！頂いちゃったね！
I got a little too much...
ふわわは、いつも……。
Fuwawa is always...
ねえ、ふわわはいつするの？パトラいつでも待ってるの！
Hey, Fuwawa, when are you going to do it? Patra, I'm waiting anytime!
ふわわ、モココのASMRが聴きたいです！
I want to hear Fuwamoco ASMR!
実はゲットでん、あの、まだ……あるんですよ！
Actually, get this... There's more!
の！言ってる！の！嘘！の！
No, you didn't! No!
大丈夫、大丈夫。今度はENの番なんだね？
It's okay, it's okay. Next time, it's EN's turn, you know?
あ、ASMRしないけど……。
I'm not doing ASMR, but...
少し、えー？えー？
Just a little bit, eh? Eh?
じゃあさ、読むからさ、ちょっと日本語でパトラちょっと読むから、
Well, I'm going to read it in Japanese, so Patra will read it in Japanese.
誰が書いたか、ちょっと当ててもらっていいですか？
Can you guess who wrote it?
えーっと、えー、フワモコのASMRって人生に不可欠だと知ってしまった今、自分はどうすればいいのかわからなくなってきました！
Fuwamoco's ASMR... I just realized it's essential to life, and now I don't know what I should do with myself.
こんな可愛い双子がベッドの中に潜り込んできて、頭をなでてくれて……。
Such cute twins crawled into bed and patted my head...
そのあとは、フワワとモコちゃんの膝の上で歌だね、
And after that, dozing off individually with Fuwawa and then on Moco-chan's lap...
このボイスは、ここくに、ここくを与えてくれるし、脳内をくすぐってくれる、
This voice track will truly bring you bliss and many tingles in your brain, and tickle your brain...
こんなふわふわで、ふわふわな体験をさせていただき、ありがとうございます！
Such a fluffy and fuzzy experience, thank you so much!
ふ、ベッドだよね？ベッドだよね？
It's a bed, right? It's a bed, right?
知ってる。知ってますか？
I know. Do you know?
あとベッドの練り水チャンスも……！
And we got the bed's rinsing chance!
すごいなんかコメントも気付いてくれて……！
Amazing, they even noticed the comments!
健全そう！よ！健全！よ！
So wholesome!
ねえ、ねえ、モコちゃんも呼んで！ねえ、呼んで、呼んで！ねえ、リサちゃーん、ボク！
Hey, hey, call Mococo too!
Fuwamoco ASMR was something I didn't know I needed,
but now that I have it I'm not sure what to do with myself...
from having the cute twins crawl into bed and pat my head,
to dozing off individually with Fuwawa and then on Moco-chan's lap... these voice tracks will truly bring you bliss and many tingles in your brain,
I am very grateful for getting to experience this wholly fluffy and fuzzy experience!
Thank you, Nerissa! Thank you! Thank you!
モコちゃんは、モコちゃんはちょっと……分からなくなっちゃったけども。
Mococo was... Mococo was...
でも、やっぱ近しい動機とかに聞かれるのは恥ずかしい、恥ずかしい！
Still, you know, being asked by close-running motives is embarrassing, embarrassing.
でもモコちゃん長文でね、そう、丁寧に送ってくれてね！
Mococo wrote it so long and carefully for us, you know?
Thank you so much! Thank you so much!
Thank you so much!
はい、今日もね、
And so today,
ね、お話も配信できて、パトラをね、ちゃんとね、こうしてね、ピーディーコラボもできて、
We were able to have a wonderful collab with Patra-san, right?
そうなのよね、パトラも幸せだった、嬉しいよー！せーの、ぽんぽん！
That's right, Patra was so happy!
こんなね、幸せ空間が来るんだったらね、
If such a happy space is coming,
なんかね、あの、ホロライブさんいつでもお仕事お待ちしております！
Hololive-san, we are waiting for your offers anytime!
パトラね、もっともっとまたやりたいです！何でもできる、ENも、そう、ね！うんうん！
Patra wants to collab more!
それでは、今日のコラボ配信はここまでとなります！
And so, today's collab stream ends here!
こんなね、幸せ空間がまたできたらいいよね、ちょっと、またコラボしてくれますか？
If such a happy space can be created, won't you collab with us again?
あたりまえだよ、可愛いー！
Of course! So cute!
それではみんな、ちょっとバイバイの時間よ！
And so everyone...
Thank you so much! Thank you so much! Thank you so much!
Thank you so much! Thank you so much!
あ、幸せじゃあ！
Ah, be happy!
3D COLLAB
[Fuwawa, Patra, Mococo - 3D Collab]